to
sailors
I told the
into the sea
me
throw
swallowed
fish
great
and a
whole,
me
me alive in
buried
and
dark.
the
because
from God
ran
I
was too wide.
mercy
His
Nineveh,
He sent me to
hated
the city I
drown than see
sooner
I'd
spared.
her
for my
came
The storm
sake;
fell on me.
lot
the
the sailors,
spare
To
me
throw
I had them
overboard.
in
buried alive
days
Three
fish.
the
Then,
I was dust,
after
long
a sign
demanded
scribes
my
them only
Jesus gave
name:
was three
Jonas
For as
in
nights
days and three
belly;
whale's
the
the Son of
shall
so
and
days
man be three
in the heart
nights
three
earth.
of the
down guilty
went
I
was mine.
storm
the
innocent,
down
went
He
what was ours;
bearing
Himself.
He gave
held
more
The grave no
held
deep
Him than the
me.
rose.
He
you've
are sure
who
You
too far
fallen
His
far
that is how
reaches.
mercy
Him the grave.
cost
It
running,
Stop
turn:
and
who went down
One
the
rose
your dark and
into
is Jesus.
again
out of the
up
Come
deep,
live.
and